<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Selena Mertvykh</title><link>https://mertvykh.gay/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Selena Mertvykh</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mertvykh.gay/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>You should probably become a weapon</title><link>https://mertvykh.gay/posts/weapon/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mertvykh.gay/posts/weapon/</guid><description>It&amp;rsquo;s morning again in America. We live in the future. O tempora! O mores!
Brynn Tannehill was right, although her timeline may have been a little pessimistic. If you&amp;rsquo;re like me at all, a sizable fraction of the population wants you dead, as in lined up and shot. They will unblinkingly accuse your suicide hotlines of being sexual predators. If you&amp;rsquo;re unlucky enough to draw the attention of some of them, they will harass you until you commit die &amp;mdash; dox you, show up outside your house, get you fired from your job &amp;mdash; for the crime of being trans on the internet, because they think it&amp;rsquo;s funny.</description><content>&lt;p>It&amp;rsquo;s morning again in America. We live in the future. &lt;em>O tempora! O mores!&lt;/em>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Brynn Tannehill was right, although her timeline may have been a little pessimistic. If you&amp;rsquo;re like me at all, a sizable fraction of the population wants you dead, &lt;a href="https://boingboing.net/2022/03/25/mississippi-republican-calls-for-killings-of-trans-people-and-supporters.html">as in lined up and shot.&lt;/a> &lt;a href="https://www.losangelesblade.com/2022/04/29/hands-off-trevor-project-suicidal-lgbtq-youth/">They will unblinkingly accuse your suicide hotlines of being sexual predators.&lt;/a> If you&amp;rsquo;re unlucky enough to draw the attention of some of them, they will harass you until you commit die &amp;mdash; dox you, show up outside your house, get you fired from your job &amp;mdash; for the crime of being trans on the internet, because they think it&amp;rsquo;s funny. The cruelty is the fucking point. It&amp;rsquo;s going to get worse.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>A sizable chunk of the queer community &amp;mdash; in the way that we predominantly relate to each other these days, i.e. social media &amp;mdash; isn&amp;rsquo;t blameless either. Isabel Fall was absolutely right and the chucklefucks who ran her into a mental ward know it.&lt;sup id="fnref:1">&lt;a href="#fn:1" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">1&lt;/a>&lt;/sup> If you follow anyone at all in the vague direction of the left you&amp;rsquo;ve heard of something like this happening.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Welcome to the Cool Zone.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Being a smartass on Twitter doesn&amp;rsquo;t fix this. Going to a protest with drag shows and people with clever signs doesn&amp;rsquo;t fix this. In this day and age the utility of a response to fascist calls for genocide is apparently measured in the number of white liberals with HRC bumper stickers that it enrages.&lt;sup id="fnref:2">&lt;a href="#fn:2" class="footnote-ref" role="doc-noteref">2&lt;/a>&lt;/sup>&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Doomscrolling doesn&amp;rsquo;t fix this either. It&amp;rsquo;s your hindbrain stuck in a feedback loop. It accomplishes very little other than destruction. It destroys your mind, your relationships, and your life, all in the name of ad revenue.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>There &lt;em>is&lt;/em> a way out. I mentioned Isabel earlier for one very specific reason. Being, as I am, a disgusting freak with disgusting body-horror fetishes, I was both horrified and aroused by Helicopter Story. It was too emotionally powerful for me to revisit for some time. When my rational brain caught up with my emotional one, I realized that I would gladly submit to tactical gender reassignment, as long as I was fighting &lt;em>against&lt;/em> the remains of the US on behalf of a trans paramilitary force or something like that. It&amp;rsquo;s not a question of being a weapon &amp;mdash; that&amp;rsquo;s going to happen one way or the other &amp;mdash; it&amp;rsquo;s a question of who you&amp;rsquo;re pointed at. &lt;a href="https://korpscon.com/">The Korps&lt;/a> explored this concept a couple years before Isabel ever did. M61 Vulcan go spinny.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The way out of the feedback loop is action. Here&amp;rsquo;s what has been the most helpful for me.&lt;/p>
&lt;ol start="0">
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Keep your body safe.&lt;/strong>
Most importantly, if you are at risk of self-harm, do whatever you must to ward that off before anything else. The rest of this advice is supposed to double as a mental health prescription, but if it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work for you then it doesn&amp;rsquo;t work.
&lt;em>(What follows is my own personal experience. I am a GPT-3 instance with a blog, not your doctor.)&lt;/em>
Having been in those trenches for a long time, I can say that sometimes the usual advice &amp;mdash; have functional coping mechanisms, go to therapy, be social, exercise, eat well, sleep well &amp;mdash; just doesn&amp;rsquo;t always work, whether for neurological or systemic reasons. Sometimes it&amp;rsquo;s like trying to start a fire with wet wood. You need a spark. Intranasal ketamine has been extremely helpful for me in that capacity. So has psilocybin. I&amp;rsquo;ve heard exciting things about MDMA as well. If you can afford to have any of these administered under controlled clinical settings, and nothing else has worked so far, it&amp;rsquo;s worth a shot. If not, mushrooms are &lt;a href="https://reddit.com/r/unclebens">probably the easiest to source.&lt;/a> Obviously do your research before you ingest any entheogen or dissociative. Don&amp;rsquo;t fly blind.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Keep your identity safe.&lt;/strong>
Back when it happened, I heard someone say, &lt;a href="https://twitter.com/Atsiko/status/1217691682315100160">&amp;ldquo;Isabel stepped on a landmine.&amp;quot;&lt;/a> This is accurate &amp;mdash; even if I want to scream, &amp;ldquo;who put the fucking landmine there, you fucking dipshits?&amp;rdquo;
Stay out of the minefield. Keep your opsec tight. Do not maintain any more than a cursory social media presence under your real name. Learn &lt;a href="https://open.nytimes.com/how-to-dox-yourself-on-the-internet-d2892b4c5954?gi=2ad9ec15db0d">how to dox yourself&lt;/a> and do it every couple months. A little paranoia goes a long way.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Train like a motherfucker.&lt;/strong>
Lifting and running have been a godsend for me, if only because they give my anger an outlet. &lt;a href="https://theanarchistlibrary.org/library/max-res-maximum-potential">There are some who will say that the apparatus of state violence doesn&amp;rsquo;t care how much you deadlift or what your mile time is.&lt;/a> That&amp;rsquo;s true, but the looming threat to your safety in coming years is probably stochastic violence, not out-and-out state violence. Some nutjob with an AR will act long before the government does. Becoming harder to kill is good praxis.
Both volumes of &lt;a href="https://www.tacticalbarbell.com/">Tactical Barbell&lt;/a> are available on libgen. It&amp;rsquo;s simple and easy to remember, and I enjoy it as much as I&amp;rsquo;ve enjoyed any regimen. If you already lift and have a program you like, far be it from me to tell you what to do.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Learn to shoot.&lt;/strong> This was something I was afraid of for a long time, owing to the whole suicidally-depressed thing. It helped. If you&amp;rsquo;re in a major urban area there&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a href="https://www.pinkpistols.org/find-a-local-chapter/">probably a leftist gun club or Discord near you.&lt;/a> If not, you &lt;a href="https://www.blazingsword.org/">may be able to find a queer-friendly instructor in your area.&lt;/a> Their politics may be too shallow or too statist for you, but it beats nothing. It should also be noted that you don&amp;rsquo;t need to own a gun yet if you don&amp;rsquo;t want to, but a couple of days at the range with a trusted friend is not a bad idea at all.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Read up.&lt;/strong> This need not be a dull affair. For theory, I like the &lt;a href="https://everything2.com/title/Rage+Against+The+Machine%2527s+recommended+reading+list">RATM reading list&lt;/a>. Hell, it wouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a bad idea to start with &lt;a href="https://youtube.com/c/thephilosophytube">Abigail Thorn&lt;/a>, who is very, very good about citing her sources. &lt;a href="https://reddit.com/r/socialistra">r/SocialistRA&lt;/a> has a very nice &lt;a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/SocialistRA/wiki/index">wiki&lt;/a> that covers many of the same points as this blog post. Between Libgen and Sci-Hub you should be able to get your hands on anything you need.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Don&amp;rsquo;t die twice.&lt;/strong> You are guaranteed to die once. Do not squelch the life within you for the purpose of your safety; your fear and self-censorship will not protect you. They already know you&amp;rsquo;re trans. They&amp;rsquo;ve already planned your death. You might as well be your entire self, immediate living conditions permitting.&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>Go forth. Contain multitudes. Tear shit up.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Flesh is temporary; the synthetic is eternal.&lt;/p>
&lt;section class="footnotes" role="doc-endnotes">
&lt;hr>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li id="fn:1" role="doc-endnote">
&lt;p>Twittersearching her name is the fastest way to find out whatever cannibalistic Internet drama is going on this week. I don&amp;rsquo;t recommend it. It&amp;rsquo;s depressing.&amp;#160;&lt;a href="#fnref:1" class="footnote-backref" role="doc-backlink">&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;li id="fn:2" role="doc-endnote">
&lt;p>Disclaimer: I&amp;rsquo;m white and I voted for HRC.&amp;#160;&lt;a href="#fnref:2" class="footnote-backref" role="doc-backlink">&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;/section></content></item></channel></rss>